You and me
내 맘이 보이지
한참을 쳐다봐
가까이 다가가
You see
1, 2, 3
용기가 생겼지
이미 아는 니 눈치
고개를 돌려 천천히
여기
You see
여기 보이니
Looking for attention
너야겠어
확실하게 나로 만들겠어
Drop the question
Drop the drop the question
Want attention
Wanna want attention
You give me butterflies
You know
내 맘은 온통 paradise
꿈에서 깨워주지 마
You got me looking for attention
가끔은 정말 헷갈리지만
분명한 건
You got me looking for attention
날 우연히 마주친 척할래
못 본 척 지나갈래
You're so fine
Gotta gotta get to know ya
You got me looking for attention
나와 나와 걸어가줘
지금 돌아서면
Need ya need ya need ya
To look at me back
Hey 다 들켰었나?
널 보면 하트가 튀어나와
난 사탕을 찾는 baby
내 맘은 설레지
Drop the question
Drop the drop the question
Want attention
Wanna want attention
You give me butterflies
You know
내 맘은 온통 paradise
꿈에서 깨워주지 마
You got me looking for attention
가끔은 정말 헷갈리지만 분명한 건
ATTENTION
ATTENTION IS WHAT I WANT